http://www.lottostrategies.com/cgi-bin/showpage/1001029/b/privacy_policy.html

Home | Bookmark | Mobile Version
» Mobile Version» Smart Pick» Quick Pick» Lotto Analysis» Wheeling System» Have I Won?» Latest Results» Numbers Archive» Pick 3/Pick 4» Current Jackpot» Jackpot Analysis» Odds Calculator» Tips & Strategies» Multi-state Lotteries» Resource Center» News & Stories» Scam Alert» Webmaster» Lottery Data Feed Premium Members» My Astro Picks» My Lotto Wheels» My Smart Picks» My Pick 3/Pick 4» My Lotto Analysis» My Lucky Numbers» My Have I Won» My Numbers Archive» My Lotto PoolMember IDPasswordForget ID/Password?Renew MembershipPrivacy Policy
LottoStrategies.com takes your privacy seriously.
There are several components to our strict Privacy Policy. Our adherence to these principles ensures that your confidentiality is protected.
Information Gathering and Use
LottoStrategies.com collects only necessary personal information - such as your name, e-mail and address - when you sign up
for account, and asks for no information we don't absolutely need to serve you.
LottoStrategies.com also automatically records your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. This information
helps us accomplish your requests, customize our content and advertising and serve you better.
Information Dissemination
LottoStrategies.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information
in any manner not disclosed in this statement. Under no circumstances will LottoStrategies.com disclose your personal information to any third parties.
Lotto Forums
LottoStrategies.com has a message board available for visitors. Please keep in mind that any information disclosed in the Lotto
Forum becomes public information. You should be cautious when decided to disclose any personal information.
Security
The sensitive personal information in your LottoStrategies.com account, such as your password, is password protected for your
privacy and security. In certain areas of the site, LottoStrategies.com uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.
Quick Lottery Reference
Atlantic Canada(AC) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Atlantic Canada(AC) Lottery Past Results,
Lotto 6/49,
Super 7,
Bucko,
Pay Day,
Pik 4,
Keno Atlantic,
Atlantic 6/49,
Tag,
Arizona(AZ) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Arizona(AZ) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Fantasy 5,
The Pick,
Pick 3,
British Columbia(BC) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
British Columbia(BC) Lottery Past Results,
Lotto 6/49,
Super 7,
BC 49,
PayDay,
Extra,
Daily 3,
California(CA) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
California(CA) Lottery Past Results,
SuperLotto Plus,
Midday 3,
MEGA Millions,
Fantasy 5,
Daily Derby,
Daily 3,
Colorado(CO) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Colorado(CO) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Lotto,
Cash 5,
Connecticut(CT) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Connecticut(CT) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Lotto,
Cash 5,
Midday 4,
Play 4,
Midday 3,
Play 3,
District of Columbia(DC) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
District of Columbia(DC) Lottery Past Results,
Hot Lotto,
DC Daily 6,
Midday 3,
Powerball,
Lucky Numbers,
Rolling Cash 5,
Midday 4,
DC 4,
Hot 5,
Delaware(DE) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Delaware(DE) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Play 4 Day,
Multi Win Lotto,
Play 3 Night,
Play 3 Day,
Play 4 Night,
Florida(FL) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Florida(FL) Lottery Past Results,
Play 4,
Mega Money,
Lotto,
Fantasy 5,
Cash 3,
Georgia(GA) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Georgia(GA) Lottery Past Results,
Win For Life,
Midday 4,
MEGA Millions,
Fantasy 5,
Cash 3,
Lotto South,
Midday 3,
Cash 4,
Iowa(IA) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Iowa(IA) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Hot Lotto,
100K Cash,
Midday 3,
Pick 4,
Midday 4,
Pick 3,
Idaho(ID) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Idaho(ID) Lottery Past Results,
Wild Card 2,
Powerball,
Pick 3,
Illinois(IL) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Illinois(IL) Lottery Past Results,
Lotto,
Midday 4,
MEGA Millions,
Little Lotto,
Pick 3,
Midday 3,
Pick 4,
Indiana(IN) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Indiana(IN) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Mix and Match,
Midday 3,
Midday 4,
Hoosier Lotto,
Lucky 5,
Pick 4,
Midday Lucky 5,
Pick 3,
Kansas(KS) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Kansas(KS) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Super Cash,
Hot Lotto,
2 By 2,
Pick 3,
Kentucky(KY) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Kentucky(KY) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Cash Ball,
Midday 4,
Midday 3,
Pick 4,
Win For Life,
TIC TAC Cash,
Pick 3,
Lotto South,
Louisiana(LA) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Louisiana(LA) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Pick 4,
Pick 3,
Cash Quest,
Lotto,
Massachusetts(MA) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Massachusetts(MA) Lottery Past Results,
MEGA Millions,
Megabucks,
Cash Winfall,
MassCash,
Numbers,
Maryland(MD) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Maryland(MD) Lottery Past Results,
MEGA Millions,
Midday 4,
Bonus Match 5,
MultiMatch,
Pick 4,
Midday 3,
Lotto,
Pick 3,
Maine(ME) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Maine(ME) Lottery Past Results,
Midday 3,
Paycheck,
Triple Play,
Megabucks,
Pick 4,
Powerball,
Midday 4,
Pick 3,
Michigan(MI) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Michigan(MI) Lottery Past Results,
MEGA Millions,
Fantasy 5,
Keno,
Midday 4,
Evening 4,
Classic Lotto 47,
Evening 3,
Midday 3,
Minnesota(MN) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Minnesota(MN) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Hot Lotto,
Daily 3,
Northstar Cash,
Gopher 5,
Missouri(MO) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Missouri(MO) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Lotto,
Midday 5,
Midday 4,
Midday 3,
Show Me 5,
Pick 3,
Pick 4,
Montana(MT) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Montana(MT) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Wild Card 2,
Hot Lotto,
Montana Cash,
North Carolina(NC) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
North Carolina(NC) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
North Dakota(ND) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
North Dakota(ND) Lottery Past Results,
Wild Card 2,
2 By 2,
Powerball,
Hot Lotto,
Nebraska(NE) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Nebraska(NE) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Pick 5,
2 By 2,
Pick 3,
New Hampshire(NH) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
New Hampshire(NH) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Megabucks,
Hot Lotto,
Paycheck,
Triple Play,
Pick 3,
Midday 3,
Pick 4,
Midday 4,
New Jersey(NJ) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
New Jersey(NJ) Lottery Past Results,
MEGA Millions,
Pick 6 Lotto,
Midday 3,
Cash 5,
Midday 4,
Pick 4,
Pick 3,
New Mexico(NM) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
New Mexico(NM) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
4 This Way,
Roadrunner Cash,
Pick 3,
New York(NY) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
New York(NY) Lottery Past Results,
Lotto,
MEGA Millions,
Pick 10,
Take 5,
Midday Win 4,
Midday Numbers,
Win 4,
Numbers,
Ohio(OH) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Ohio(OH) Lottery Past Results,
MEGA Millions,
Rolling Cash 5,
Lot O Play,
Classic Lotto,
Kicker,
Midday 3,
Midday 4,
Pick 4,
Pick 3,
Oklahoma(OK) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Oklahoma(OK) Lottery Past Results,
Pick 3,
Cash 5,
Powerball,
Ontario(ON) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Ontario(ON) Lottery Past Results,
Lotto 6/49,
Early Bird,
PayDay,
Super 7,
Lottario,
Ontario 49,
Pick 3,
Pick 4,
Encore,
Keno,
Oregon(OR) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Oregon(OR) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Pick 4
4PM,
Win for Life,
Pick 4
1PM,
Lucky Lines,
Pick 4
7PM,
Megabucks,
Pick 4
10PM,
Pennsylvania(PA) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Pennsylvania(PA) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Lucky For Life,
Match 6 Lotto,
Cash 5,
Midday Number,
Midday Big 4,
Big 4,
Daily Number,
Quebec(QC) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Quebec(QC) Lottery Past Results,
Quebec 49,
Super 7,
La Mini,
Banco,
Lotto 6/49,
Extra,
La Quotidienne 3,
La Quotidienne 4,
Joker,
Rhode Island(RI) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Rhode Island(RI) Lottery Past Results,
Wild Money,
The Numbers,
Powerball,
South Carolina(SC) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
South Carolina(SC) Lottery Past Results,
Midday 4,
Palmetto Cash 5,
Powerball,
Midday 3,
Evening Pick 3,
Evening Pick 4,
South Dakota(SD) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
South Dakota(SD) Lottery Past Results,
Powerball,
Hot Lotto,
Wild Card 2,
Dakota Cash,
Tennessee(TN) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Tennessee(TN) Lottery Past Results,
Lotto 5,
Powerball,
Cash 4,
Midday 4,
Midday 3,
Cash 3,
Texas(TX) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Texas(TX) Lottery Past Results,
MEGA Millions,
Cash 5,
Lotto Texas,
Two Step,
Pick 3 Day,
Pick 3 Night,
,
United Kingdom(UK) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Winning Numbers.
United Kingdom(UK) Lottery Past Results,
Lotto 6/49,
Euro Millions,
Thunderball,
HotPicks,
Daily Play,
Dream Number,
Virginia(VA) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Virginia(VA) Lottery Past Results,
MEGA Millions,
Midday Cash 5,
Win For Life,
Midday 3,
Pick 4,
Cash 5,
Pick 3,
Midday 4,
Lotto South,
Vermont(VT) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Vermont(VT) Lottery Past Results,
Paycheck,
Triple Play,
Megabucks,
Midday 4,
Powerball,
Pick 3,
Pick 4,
Midday 3,
Washington(WA) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Washington(WA) Lottery Past Results,
Quinto,
MEGA Millions,
Lotto,
Daily Game,
Keno,
Western Canada(WC) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Western Canada(WC) Lottery Past Results,
Western 49,
Lotto 6/49,
Extra,
Pick 3,
Prairie Keno,
Super 7,
Wisconsin(WI) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
Wisconsin(WI) Lottery Past Results,
Badger 5,
Powerball,
Super Cash,
Pick 3,
Pick 4,
Megabucks,
West Virginia(WV) State Lotto Lottery Information,
Winning Numbers.
West Virginia(WV) Lottery Past Results,
Hot Lotto,
Powerball,
Cash 25,
Daily 4,
Daily 3,
Home |About Us |Tell a Friend |Site Map |Privacy Policy |Terms of Service |Webmaster |Related Links |Contact Us
